[Service Description]

1. Auto-Subscription Service
  1.1 Service Names: Weekly Subscription (1 week), Monthly Subscription (1 month), Yearly Subscription (1 year)
  1.2 Service Prices: Monthly Subscription at $1.99 per month, Quarterly Subscription at $3.99 per quarter, Yearly Subscription at $12.99 per year

3. Payment: Users will confirm their purchase and make payment through their iTunes account.

3. Auto-renewal of Subscribed Accounts: For users who have purchased the auto-subscription membership, the account will be charged 24 hours before the expiration of each monthly subscription period, and the subscription will be extended for another subscription cycle upon successful payment.

4. To Cancel Renewal: To cancel the auto-renewal feature, please manually disable it in the iTunes/Apple ID device management at least 24 hours before the current subscription period ends.